<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on kmaris</title>
    <link>https://kmaris.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on kmaris</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 09:38:19 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kmaris.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Repairing your Morrowind destiny</title>
      <link>https://kmaris.net/posts/morrow-repair-destiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 07:35:53 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmaris.net/posts/morrow-repair-destiny/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, I still play Morrowind (with OpenMW) and love to use mods like Tamriel Rebuilt, Wyrmhaven, Beware the Sixth House, etc. In my case I installed a mod, on a fresh character!, that changed buildings (Beautiful Cities of Morrowind). Upon entering the Ald Skar Inn, whom do I find? Nobody. Nada. Bupkiss.
Weird, I thought. It was at the momentary epiphany that I started falling through the ground. And FAST. And PASSING other unforunates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iTerm2, ssh, and remote tmux session integration for vim</title>
      <link>https://kmaris.net/posts/iterm2-tmux-ssh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:12:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmaris.net/posts/iterm2-tmux-ssh/</guid>
      <description>If you often use vim, especially while working on remote servers, you know how annoying getting mouse integration to work is. Here is what I have found works best for me. What I wanted was:
Functional ⌘-C and ⌘-V for copy/paste into and out of the terminal. Copy/paste needs to work with tmux running on the remote host. Mouse scrolling still works in some form. Mouse scroll is the thing that suffers here, for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Github Actions Deploy Key</title>
      <link>https://kmaris.net/posts/gh-actions-deploy-key/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 09:47:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmaris.net/posts/gh-actions-deploy-key/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip; and how to use it to deploy a static website. Well, I ran out of patience with my own static website generator. While I do plan to finish it, in the meantime I won&amp;rsquo;t be using it to generate this website. So, for now it&amp;rsquo;s hugo. Nowthen, how to get it deployed? I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to try it with Github Actions for a while and this seemed like a nice fit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tea titbit</title>
      <link>https://kmaris.net/posts/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 10:15:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kmaris.net/posts/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ll see how long I keep this up, but it is something I&amp;rsquo;ve needed to do for a while now. The majority of these posts will probably refer to my software/tech side of life. But for now I&amp;rsquo;ll just get it all started off with a fact about tea:
There is a special name for when tea leaves uncurl as hot water is poured over them. It is called “the agony of the leaves.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
